1apps.com 2017-12-23

# Welcome to 1Apps The Premier Free Hosting Site

1Apps.net has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This statement sets forth our information gathering and dissemination practices for the 1Apps.net site.

**  
What This Privacy Policy Covers**

·      This policy covers how 1Apps.net treats personal information that we collects and receive.  Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, email address, IP address and that is not otherwise publicly available.

·      This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 1Apps.net does not own or control, or to people that 1Apps.net does not employ or manage.

**What We Collect and Where**

 Our site uses several different forms that our customers can use to request information, products, and services. From these forms, we collect the following information:

 ·      Visitors' contact information

·      Unique identifiers

·      IP addresses

**  
 Children  
**

The 1Apps.net service is not available for anyone who is under the age of 13 and are not allowed to register and become a member of 1Apps.net. This web site is not directed at children under 13 years of age.  ** **

**What Do We Use This Information For?**

**Contact Information  
**  
We use your contact information to send you information about your account and to get in touch with you when necessary. 

Customers can update contact information on 1Apps.net at any time.

**IP addresses  
**  
We use your unique network address (IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site.

**Cookies** We may use "cookies" to track how users use our web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a web server can store on the users' computer and use to identify the user should they visit the web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that users provide us through our web site.  We gather this information for internal use only and will never authorize the release of this information with anyone.

·  Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

· Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy  

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).   

**Edit and Delete Your Account Information.**  

·      You can edit your account information at any time.

·      You can delete your 1Apps.net account at anytime by logging into your control panel.

  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

 1Apps.net may update this privacy policy at any time. If we update our privacy policy the changes will be displayed on this page.  ** **

**Linked Sites  
**  
This site contains links to external web sites. 1Apps.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these web sites.
